Ooh, no, no
No, no
I can tell you're bitter, babe
It's like being on the outside of an inside joke
It's like when they only got Pepsi and you really want Coke
It's like you finally get a text back and it's just your mom
It's like when you just broke up and they play your song
I know they said it's kinda stupid
But it's just the way I'm feeling right now
And I hate that I could tell that someone's
Probably in my shoes by now, right now
I know she thinkin' that she found herself a winner
I know you fucked her on the counter right before you cooked hеr dinner, yeah
I know you think about me whеn you kiss her
I left a taste in your mouth, can she taste me now
That you threw out all our furniture and pictures?
I bet you sugarcoat the truth, I bet you're real sweet with her, yeah
I know you think about me when you kiss her
I left a taste in your mouth, can she taste me now?
I'm bitter
I'm bitter, I'm bitter, I'm bitter, I'm bitter (ooh, nah)
I think about you when I kiss her
But I tell her I love her, when I fuck her, I don't miss ya
The past is the past and you're so last year
It's not like we would last, girl, you made that clear
I say I don't fuck with you, babe
I can tell that you're bitter, yeah
Talk shit about me to your friends (I still don't fuck with you, babe)
You was in the bed (uh), you probably right (uh)
You're in my head, every night, every night (uh)
I know she thinkin' that she found herself a winner
I know you fucked her on the counter right before you cooked her dinner, yeah
I know you think about me when you kiss her
I left a taste in your mouth, can she taste me now
That you threw out all our furniture and pictures?
I bet you sugarcoat the truth, I bet you're real sweet with her, yeah
I know you think about me when you kiss her
I left a taste in your mouth, can she taste me now?
I'm bitter
I'm bitter, I'm bitter, I'm bitter, I'm bitter
(Yeah, you're bitter, I could tell, uh)
You're still in my head, but
You're not in my bed now
You're not in my bed now (you're not in my bed now)
You're still in my head, but
You're not in my bed now
You're not in my bed now (you're not in my bed now)
I know she thinkin' that she found herself a winner (she did)
I know you fucked her on the counter right before you cooked her dinner, yeah
I know you think about me when you kiss her
I left a taste in your mouth, can she taste me now
That you threw out all our furniture and pictures?
I bet you sugarcoat the truth, I bet you're real sweet with her, yeah
I know you think about me when you kiss her
I left a taste in your mouth, can she taste me now?
I'm bitter
I'm bitter, I'm bitter, I'm bitter, I'm bitter (I bet you miss me, bet you miss me)
I bet you miss me, bet you miss me (ooh, ooh, I'm bitter)
I bet you miss me, bet you miss me (I'm bitter, I'm bitter, I'm bitter, I'm bitter)
Can tell you miss me, tell you miss me